

César Augusto Ferreira Cáceres

Address: CARRERA 21 # 29 – 103 HOYO EN UNO casa 2 Floridablanca Santander, COLOMBIA

Post code: 680001

Telephone: +57 3182405816

E-mail: Memacaceres@hotmail.com

Skype: tokyo-london2

Gender: Masculine Date of birth: 15 Oct. 91 Nationality: Colombian.

Objective

Social communicator, journalist and specialist in Human Talent Management, interested in strategically use the media in order to convey to the public the information in an appropriate manner, relevant, accurate and responsible. All this in order to apply the knowledge gained during my career with the ethical values and professional ethics.

I gained experience in the media, through social campaigns performed worldwide, around issues like kidnapping, using social networks and television as vital tools for a massive amplification and capturing international attention, monitoring corporate image in the media and internal work in the area of Human Resources, in order to avoid any kind of crisis that may affect the reputation of the organization in which I served.

Also, I had the possibility of interview different personalities like Paris Hilton, David Guetta, Nicky Romero, Pilar Castaño, Steve Aoki, Hernan Zajar, Xilena Aycardi and Moska.

Experience

Human Resources Coordinator and Marketing Coordinator

CONFECCIONES EL NOGAL Ltda., Floridablanca (Colombia)

01/01/2011 - 05/08/2014

Develop different strategies focused on improving HR policies, processes, and practices and recommending changes to HR management. Also, my work involved addressing issues raised by current employees and new-hires, organizing and scheduling orientations, and coordinating other HR functions such as training and development.

Social management and marketing assistant

CLÍNICA FOSCAL INTERNACIONAL, Bucaramanga (Colombia)

1/12/2014 - 30/04/2015

Worked at the public relations, human resources, and internal communications areas of this international clinic.

Coordinator of communications

NGO TECHO COLOMBIA, Bogotá (Colombia)

28/06/2014 - 28/10/2014

Worked in different activities at the communication and press area of this NGO, such as Identify and develop relationships with media personnel, community partners and agencies to promote our services and events.

Homeless Ministry Christian Service

SHENANDOAH VALLEY ACADEMY, Virginia (United States of America) 01/10/2008 - 14/05/2009

Social community service for the people that lived in Virginia during the junior High School year. I made part of the human resource committee and traveled as a mission trip to help people affected by THE HURICANE KATRINA that hit Texas at that time.

Journalist

UNIVERSIDAD DE LA SABANA, Chia (Colombia)

01/01/2012 - 31/12/2012



IGH hotels management training

HOLIDAY INN EXPRESS – CROWNE PLAZA WEST, Chengdu (China)

29/10/2017 - 29/04/2018

Guest relations, language training (Spanish) to the staff at the human resources department and English to guests and special clients. Inspection of services and quality of products.

Marketing intern

AIESEC - AURORA TRAVEL, Hanoi (Vietnam)

10/01/2017 - 10/07/2017

Develop AIESEC Leadership Development Experience with AURORA TRAVEL making different marketing strategies and Supporting Human Resources Department into the creation off communication tools for the workers, and also promoting Social Media in order to make the brand viral around the world.

Academic Background

Specialization in Human Resources Management

(Pontifica Universidad Javeriana – Bogotá, Colombia)

01/12/2016

Status: Graduate.

Diplomat of Strategic and Communication Management

(Universidad de la Sabana – Bogotá, Colombia)

01/05/2015

Status: Graduate.

Social Communication and Journalism

(Universidad de la Sabana – Bogotá, Colombia)

01/05/2015

Status: Graduate.

General English

(Chamber Colleg - Gzira, Malta)

19/06/2014

Status: Holiday English Advanced C1.

English Studies

(Shenandoah Valley Academy – Virginia, United States of America)

31/12/2009

Status: Fullfiled.

High School

(Colegio New Cambridge – Floridablanca, Colombia)

30/06/2007

Status: Graduate.

High School (Cont.)

(Colegio Gimnasio Piedemonte – Bucaramanga, Colombia)

31/12/2008

Status: Graduate.



Knowledge

Native language: Spanish.

Other languages: English C1 (Listening Comprehension, Reading Comprehension, Spoken Interaction, Oral Expression, Written Expression). Chinese (Basic).

Communication Skills: Good communication skills gained through my studies as social communicator and for my personal training acquired in trips abroad.

Management: Ability to organize social events at the enterprise level. Creativity, fulfillment and development of activities related to my career.

Competitions related to the job: Leadership skills, proactivity, good personal presentation, management of improvisation, vocals, accuracy of information, which is built, good camera work, creativity, recursive, good writing.

Computing Skills: Office tools (Word, Excel, Access), Photoshop and Illustrator.